{
    "subject": "resource/Mid-City_Community_Advocacy_Network_(Mid-City_CAN)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mid-City_Community_Advocacy_Network_(Mid-City_CAN)",
    "human_readable": "The Mid-City Community Advocacy Network (Mid-City CAN) is the primary topic of.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986441433429718,
            "question": "What is the primary topic of the Mid-City Community Advocacy Network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8864777684211731,
            "question": "Where is the Mid-City Community Advocacy Network based?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7700350880622864,
            "question": "What type of organization is the Mid-City Community Advocacy Network?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7485665082931519,
            "question": "Who might be involved with the Mid-City CAN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7141228318214417,
            "question": "What issues might the Mid-City CAN focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6659747362136841,
            "question": "What impact might the Mid-City CAN have on its community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5903576016426086,
            "question": "What are some potential goals of the Mid-City CAN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5864022970199585,
            "question": "What does 'CAN' stand for in the name Mid-City CAN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5480509996414185,
            "question": "Are there any similar organizations to the Mid-City CAN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40205225348472595,
            "question": "How does the Mid-City CAN work to achieve its goals?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Mid-City Community Advocacy Network (Mid-City CAN) is the primary topic of.",
            "html": "dbpedia_939_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any similar organizations to the Mid-City CAN?",
            "html": "dbpedia_939_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What does 'CAN' stand for in the name Mid-City CAN?",
            "html": "dbpedia_939_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential goals of the Mid-City CAN?",
            "html": "dbpedia_939_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_939_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents mention and describe the Mid-City Community Advocacy Network (Mid-City CAN), making it the primary topic of these documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents clearly discusses activities and details related to Mid-City Community Advocacy Network (Mid-City CAN), making it evident that this organization is the primary topic."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}